webdamdb.com 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy - WebDAM

WebDAM is firmly committed to maintaining your privacy. We strive to uphold the highest privacy standards on the web. This privacy policy is provided to explain what information we collect and how it is used in order to continue to provide you with exceptional service.

By visiting the WEBDAM.COM SITE (the “Site”), subscribing to our services (WebDAM), or making purchases through the Site, you accept the practices described in this privacy policy. Any user registered for an account, or subscription, with WebDAM.com is considered a “Customer of WebDAM.com” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. Changes to the WebDAM.com Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so check back regularly.

**WHAT AND HOW IS INFORMATION COLLECTED BY WEBDAM.COM?**

WebDAM.com collects the following personal information:

**MEMBERSHIP INFORMATION**

When registering for an account with WebDAM.com, we collect your name, email address, street address, phone number, fax number, company, web address, and the username and password that you select. This information can be updated by logging into your WebDAM.com admin console.

**PURCHASE INFORMATION**

When making purchases through WebDAM.com or a WebDAM.com website, we collect information relevant to the purchase including shipping address, billing address, name, email address, phone number, and payment details including credit card information. WebDAM.com customers may choose to use PayPal to complete payment transactions. These Privacy Policies do not apply for any personal or payment information entered at PayPal.com. Please see PayPal’s privacy policy for more information.

**OTHER USER INFORMATION**

WebDAM.com customers can create accounts for their own customers, clients, and colleagues from within their WebDAM.com website. This information includes name, email address, street address, phone number, fax number, company or studio name, web address, username, and a selected password. This information can be edited by logging into the WebDAM.com account for which the user account was created.

**COOKIES**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your Web Browser on your hard drive when browsing a website. Like most companies, WebDAM.com uses cookies to enhance your online experience. For example, cookies provide a way for us to remember your account information and log you in automatically when revisiting the Site or automatically populate your billing information when making purchasing. Cookies also provide statistical information that allows us to improve our service based on your preferences and usage behaviors. Web browsers usually accept cookies automatically; however you can change your browser settings to block cookies. By not accepting cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of the features of the Site including making purchases.

**INTERNET PROTOCOL (IP) ADDRESS**

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer that identifies you when browsing the internet. WebDAM.com collects IP addresses to generate statistical information regarding general demographics and website traffic patterns. This information is used to improve our service and make it more interesting for you based on general usage statistics. This information may also be used for system administration or diagnostic purposes or to enforce compliance with the Site’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policies.

**HOW DOES WEBDAM.COM USE COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

WebDAM.com never sells, trades, or rents your personal information to others and only shares your information with third-party companies that provide services to the Site (such as credit card merchants, partner labs, etc). WebDAM.com may share statistical information about customers, sales, or website traffic but this will never contain personal, identifiable information. We may use the information we collect to periodically inform you of changes to your account or order status, or inform you about special promotions or changes specific to the WebDAM.com service.

When making purchases through a WebDAM.com customer website, WebDAM.com does provide that customer with details regarding the purchaser’s personal information such as email address, street address, and phone number. Payment details are not kept on file and never disclosed. WebDAM.com customers are required to abide by the WebDAM.com Privacy Policy.

WebDAM.com provides a way to email an image or a collection of images to a friend. A name and email address for the friend is required to use this feature. This information is used to send a one-time email and is then discarded.

**HOW DOES WEBDAM.COM PROTECT COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

All membership information, sales transactions, and other personal details are stored in a secure, firewall-protected database. Access to personal information is limited to personnel authorized to use such information for administrative purposes only. Member’s account passwords are encrypted and can never be retrieved. All e-commerce transactions take place across secure server software (SSL) encryption.

**HOW TO PROTECT YOUR ACCOUNT?**

Never give out your account password. If you have forgotten your password, a new one will be automatically generated for you by using the “Forgot my password” link on the login page. You should change your password as soon as you login with this automatically generated password. Always use the logout link when you are finished updating or making changes to your account. In addition, always close the browser window that you were working within before leaving your computer.

**SPECIAL NOTE TO WEBDAM.COM CUSTOMERS**

WebDAM.com reserves the right to link directly to your WebDAM.com website from our product website (WebDAM.com) or in other marketing materials such as emails, brochures, or newsletters for promotional or demonstrative purposes or to include customer name in company press releases. WebDAM.com reserves the right to list customer names in client lists. To opt out if this, please email our Customer Support team at [support@webdam.com.](mailto:support@webdamsolutions.com)

**ONLINE DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

If you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of the Site such as on your About or Contact page or on message boards, we cannot control how that information may be used by third-parties. This information may be collected by third-parties to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements, or for other purposes so please do so with caution.

**CHILDREN UNDER 13**

WebDAM.com is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and such persons are strictly prohibited from using the WebDAM.com website or services.

WebDAM.com welcomes your feedback. For questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please send an email to [support@webdam.com.](mailto:support@webdamsolutions.com)
